Guide to the John W. Gardner Papers SC0908
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-161
  - Stanford Speeches, 1969-2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Bibliographies of Works by Gardner, 1938-2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Excerpts from Gardner's Writings, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Writings, 1988-2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bill and Jean Lane Memorial Gifts, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - John Hennessy Commencement Speech, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Hawaii Executive Conference Memorial Materials, 1999-2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Leadership Grant, 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Service – New York, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Dulce Carothers, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Tributes, Memorials, Obituaries, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Service-D.C. (?), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Corporation Memorial Service (New York), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Service-Stanford, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Tributes, Memorials, Obituaries-Carnegie Corporation, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Scott Harshbarger letter to Aida Gardner re: Memorial, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Announcement of Gardner's Death to Stanford Trustees, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Service-Washington, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Services-Washington DC New York, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Service – Stanford-Planning and Logistics, 1995-2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence/papers re: Gardner's death, memorials, etc., 1998-2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Biographical Sketches/Information, 1976-2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - List of Awards and Honors, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - List of Affiliations, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - List of Oral Histories, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - John W. Gardner Memorial Service, March 5, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Kirsts- Memorial Reception, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Memorial-Expenses/Bills/Invoices, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Copies of letters sent to the family, tributes, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Attendees of Gardner's Funeral (?), undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Service-Stanford, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Memorial Service Attendees, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Letters/Notes to the Family, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Memorial Service-Stanford- Transcript, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Memorial Service-Stanford-Programs, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Memorial Service- Stanford-Invitations, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - The Stanford Daily, 2/19/2002 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - The Stanford Daily, 2/21/2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Stanford Daily, 2/22/2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Report, 2/20/2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Report, 2/27/2002 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Science, 3/22/2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Chronicle of Philanthropy, 3/7/2002 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Report, 3/6/2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Associated Press Online, 2/17/2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Independent Sector Website, 2/24/2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Times, 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Newsday, Inc., 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Newsweek Website, 2/20/2002 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - The New York Times, 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New York Times, 2/20/2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto Daily News, 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Palo Alto Weekly, 2/22/2002 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Palo Alto Weekly, 2/27/2002 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer, 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - The Press-Enterprise (Riverside, CA), 2/19/2002 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - The Record (Bergen County, NJ), 2/20/2002 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - San Jose Mercury News, 2/17/2002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - San Jose Mercury News, 2/20/2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - St. Louis Post-Dispatch, 2/19/2002 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Stanford University News Service, 2/17/2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - The State (Columbia, SC), 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Newswire, Inc., 2/17/2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - United Press International, 2/17/2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - The Wall Street Journal, 2/21/2002 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - The Washington Post, 2/18/2002 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - The Washington Post, 2/19/2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Fred Wertheimer's Statement, 2/17/2002 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Lists of Honorary Degrees, 1956-2000 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Honorary Degrees-Correspondence and Related Material, 1958-2000 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Lists of Honorary Degrees and Awards, 1956-1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Honors, 1950s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Awards and Honors, 1960s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Awards and Honors, 1956-2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - American Dental Association Honorary Membership, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Awards and Honors, 1960s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Kauffman Foundation Commendation, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Case Currents-John Gardner: Jefferson Medalist, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - College Entrance Examination Board Medal- Awarded JG, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Humanitarian Father of the Year Award, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - David and Minnie Berk Foundation Max Berg Award, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Interviews, 1970-1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - JWG Interview, Biographical Summary, Review of Writings, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Lists of Interviews, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Interviews 2 (including correspondence), 1940s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "Dealings with President Carter" [Draft for Memoirs], 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - John W. Gardner Oral Histories Interviews, 1987-1998 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - John W. Gardner Oral Histories Interviews, 1987-1998 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Corporation Oral History with John W. Gardner, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Video, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Julie Plaut-Doctoral Dissertation, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Daran Wastchak-Dissertation, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Lydia Bronte Interview, 1987-1989 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lydia Bronte Interview, 1987-1989 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - LBJ Oral History, 1970s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Oral Histories, 1990-1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - List of Oral Histories, 1974-1998 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - JWG Interviews, 1991-2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - JWG Biographical Info, 1950s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Annual Lecturer's Reports, Grant Request, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "The Laughing Joss," 1929 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - JWG Memoirs, 1930s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - JWG Bios, 1960s-2000s (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - JWG Affiliations, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - JWG Video Transcript, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Book Reviews/Comments, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Mentees," 1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "Who's Who" type Biographies, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - White House Fellows Annual Meeting, October 2002 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Special Letters, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Tributes, Memorials, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Dulce Carothers' Correspondence-Outgoing, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with Jimmy Carter, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with Lady Bird Johnson, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence with Bill Moyers, 1990-2000 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Photos of JWG, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Tribute to Gardner-San Jose Mercury News, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - "A Call for Social Cohesion, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - "In Search of the Fourth Maxim," 1998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - "Leadership in the Cities," 1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "Self-Renewal," The Futurist, Nov/Dec 1996 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Mihaly Csikzentmihalyi Interview, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Gardner Fellows Brochure, 2002/2003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "Personal Renewal," 9/1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Letter to Kellog Foundation (excerpt), undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Building Community," Fall 1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "The Dimensions of Leadership," Winter 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "Rekindling the American Spirit," Sept/Oct 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - "Themes," undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Notes for Quest Scholars Seminar, 7/2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "Personal Renewal," undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - "My Career," 6/2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Speeches, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "An Argument for Student Public Service," 10/1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Haas-Related Writings/Speeches, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "The College Experience Ahead," 3/1965 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Quotations, 1970s-2000s (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Quotations [binder], 1960s-2000s (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "No Easy Victories," 1968 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Life on the Learning Curve: A John W. Gardner Reader [binder], 1998-2000, (folder 1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Life on the Learning Curve: A John W. Gardner Reader [binder], 1998-2000, (folder 2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Life on the Learning Curve: A John W. Gardner Reader combined with NORTHSTAR [binder], 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Quotation Collection [binder], undated (folder 1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Quotation Collection [binder], undated (folder 2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Alliance for National Renewal-Guide Directory, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "Wealthy and Wise," 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "The Marketization of Welfare," 1993 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Directors and Trustees," 1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "Philanthropy and Outcomes," 1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Associates Directory, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Reflections on the Challenge of Philanthropy: Health Affairs," undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "The Public Service: A Continuing Agenda," 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "The Common Cause Manual on Money and Politics," 1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 106th Congress Congressional Directory, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - White House Fellows Directory, 1977-78 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - White House Fellows Association Directory, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - White House Fellows Association Directory, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "Building Community," CFSV Annual Report, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Foreword to "Regional Stewardship: A Commitment to Place," 2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "National Renewal," 1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "Building Community," 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - "Toward a Pluralistic but Coherent Society," 1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "American Renewal," 1994 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Reinventing Community," 1992 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Leadership Papers 1-4, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Leadership Papers 5-8, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Leadership Papers 9-12, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "National Renewal," National Civic Review, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Washington Memorial Invitations, Program, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Grassroots Treetops," 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "The John W. Gardner Leadership Award," 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Ads for "Living, Leading, and the American Dream," circa 2003 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - America's Promise, Fall 2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - JG Speech Index 1965- [binder], 1937-2001 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - JG Speech Index 1965- [binder], 1937-2001 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Favorite John W. Gardner Quotes (for PBS film), 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Writings of John W. Gardner, 1988-2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "The Wisdom of John Gardner: Selected Writings" (Notes), circa 2002 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "The Wisdom of John Gardner: Selected Writings," 2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Information Quotes, 1970s-2000s (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - National Civic League Materials, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University School of Education (SUSE) Employee Manual [binder], 1997 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University School of Education (SUSE) Employee Manual [binder], 1997 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Civic Ventures, circa 2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - "Ralph Bunche: An American Odyssey" [printout for educators], 2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Collection of Quotes, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Speeches Needed Lists, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Book Orders (For JWG Books), 1987-2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Permissions, 1990s-2000s (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Memorial Service Announcements, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Scarsdale Town Club Public Service Award Programs, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Athletic Board-Distinguished Achievement Medal, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Education Commission of the United States-James Bryant Conant Award Programs, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Service Programs, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Memorial Service Programs, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Memorial Service Programs (Not Gardner), 1987-2002 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "Living, Leading, and the American Dream," (Book Advertisement) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Washington, D.C. Memorial Service Programs, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Washington, D.C. Memorial Service Announcements, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Books:
    - Self-Renewal: The Individual and the Innovative Society [Revised edition, 2 copies], 1995 (Box 23)
    - Excellence: Can We Be Equal and Excellent Too? [Revised edition, 2 copies], 1995 (Box 23)
    - In Common Cause [Revised edition, special printing for Common Cause members], 1973 (Box 23)
    - The Recovery of Confidence [2 copies], 1971 (Box 23)
    - Self-Renewal: The Individual and the Innovative Society [Revised edition], 1981 (Box 23)
    - Quotations of Wit and Wisdom, 1975 (Box 23)
    - Quotations of Wit and Wisdom [2 copies], 1996 (Box 23)
    - Toward A Motivated Society [Japanese edition, 2 copies], 1978 (Box 23)
    - Self-Renewal [Hardcover edition, 2 copies], 1963 (Box 23)
    - Morale [Hardcover First edition], 1978 (Box 23)
    - Excellence [Hardcover Revised Edition, 2 copies], 1984 (Box 23)
    - The Recovery of Confidence [Hardcover First edition], 1970 (Box 23)
    - On Leadership [Hardcover], 1990 (Box 24)
    - On Leadership [2 copies], 1993 (Box 24)
    - Living, Leading, and the American Dream [Hardcover, 2 copies], 2003 (Box 24)
    - Know or Listen to Those Who Know: A Book of Quotations [Hardcover First ed.], 1975 (Box 24)
    - No Easy Victories [Hardcover], 1968 (Box 24)
  - Videocassettes:
    - John Gardner: How to Transform Trustees and Staff into a Team (Box 25)
    - Interview with Liz Kniss, 2000 (Box 25)
    - Voices from South Africa: Carnegie Corporation of New York and its History in South Africa (Box 25)
    - Kauffman's Thoughts for the Board of Directors, 2000 (Box 25)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American ("PAL Format"), 2000 (Box 25)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American (copy 1 of 2), 2000 (Box 25)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American (copy 2 of 2), 2000 (Box 25)
    - The White House Fellows Program "The Opportunity of a Lifetime" (Box 25)
    - John Gardner Archival Tape Compilation Reel, 1964-1980 (Box 25)
    - "The Release of Human Possibilities" Volume One (Box 25)
    - Cable Co-Op Presents an Interview with Dr. John Gardner, 2000 (Box 25)
    - "Nightwatch" Interview with John W. Gardner, 1989 (Box 25)
    - SAC Video 323 Leadership Makes the Difference, 1977 (Box 25)
    - John Gardner Life on the Learning Curve (Box 25)
    - Housing 60s vs 90s (CNN), 1999 (Box 25)
    - Speech by Dr. John Gardner at the V Corps Commanders' Conference at the Sauerland Stern Hotel, Willingen Federal Republic of Germany, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Independent Sector John W. Gardner Leadership Award (Box 26)
    - Annual Meeting "John Gardner Award," 1991 (Box 26)
    - A Conversation with John Gardner (Box 26)
    - How to Transform Trustees and Staff into a Team (Box 26)
    - The Haas Center for Public Service Reflections on the First 15 Years, 2000 (Box 26)
    - Self Renewal, 2000 (Box 26)
    - Issues and Ideas: Achieving Self-Renewal, 2000 (Box 26)
    - Remarks by President Clinton, John Gardner Doris Kearns Goodwin at Press Conference on Political Reform, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Sharon Bray Interview w/John Gardner, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Dr. John Gardner Reflecting on Renewal, 1999 (Box 26)
    - Columbia University Carnegie Corp. Project John Gardner Reel #1, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Columbia University Carnegie Corp. Project John Gardner Reel #2, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Columbia University Carnegie Corp. Project John Gardner Reel #3, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Columbia University Carnegie Corp. Project John Gardner Reel #4, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Columbia University Carnegie Corp. Project John Gardner Reel #5, 1998 (Box 26)
    - David Mathews Interview with John Gardner on "Leadership," 1987 (Box 27)
    - John W. Gardner – A Life Devoted to Excellence Self Renewal, 1993 (Box 27)
    - White House Fellows Gala Dinner, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Annual Conference Gardner Award Luncheon, 1999 (Box 27)
    - White House Rose Garden Brief speech by Clinton Then JG All American Cities Awards, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Dr. John Gardner "Renewal of a Nation" The Forum Club of Houston Eugene H. Vaughan Jr., Chairman, Presiding, 1993 (Box 27)
    - John Gardner Thoughts on Governance (Box 27)
    - World Affairs Report Guest: John Gardner (Ron Hilton), 1999 (Box 27)
    - Dr. John Gardner: Organizational Effectiveness, Leadership, Citizenship and Philanthropy (Box 27)
    - Dr. John Gardner Reflecting on Leadership, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Ten and Counting (Box 27)
  - Rolodex Cards:
    - Rolodex Cards (Box 28)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American [Film Project]-Advertisement in Current, August 6, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American [Film Project]-Article in Stanford Report, September 26, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American [Film Project]-Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American [Film Project]-Carriage Report, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - John Gardner: Uncommon American [Film Project]-Promotional Material, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - "The White House Fellows Association: A Legacy of Leadership," circa 1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - The White House Fellows Association-Promotional Material (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - "News from the White House Fellows Association," Spring 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - The White House Fellows Association-Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Common Cause-Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Common Cause-Publications, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Common Cause-Planning Documents, 1999-2001 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Common Cause-Memoranda, Press Releases, Clippings, circa 1998-2001 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Clippings about Public Service, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - John Gardner Public Service Fellows [listings], 1985-2001 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Giving Back to the Future Program, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - The White House Fellows Association-Program, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Haas Center-Administrative, 1989-2001 (folder 1 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Haas Center-Administrative, 1989-2001 (folder 2 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Haas Center-Administrative, 1989-2001 (folder 3 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - John Gardner Public Service Fellowship, 1985-1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Haas Center-Annual Reports, 1994-1997 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Haas Center-Miscellaneous Publications, 1996-2000 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Common Cause-Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Audiocassettes/Compact Discs:
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Sandra Hernandez, 4/03/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Sandra Hernandez, 4/03/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Steve Kirsch, 5/15/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Steve Kirsch, 5/15/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Jed Emerson, 4/29/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Jed Emerson, 4/29/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Iqbal Paroo, 4/15/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Iqbal Paroo, 4/15/2003 (Box 31)
    - Rob Reich Brown Bag Philanthropy Series, 1/31/2002 (Box 31)
    - Rob Reich – Brown Bag, 1/31/2002 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Steven Schroeder, 2/25/2003 (Box 31)
    - Brown Bag Philanthropy Series Steven Schroeder (Box 31)
    - Remembering John Gardner NPR, 2/18/2002 (Box 31)
    - NAB – Faculty Focus Group, 1/6/1998 (Box 31)
    - NAB – Faculty Focus Group, 1/6/1998 (Box 31)
    - Faculty Focus Group, 1/9/1998 (Box 31)
    - Unlabeled Compact Discs (3) (Box 31)
  - Data Storage Media:
    - 3 1/2" Floppy Disks, 3 1/2" SyQuest Hard Disk, Zip Drive Disks (Box 32)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-111
  - Personality Files, Ac-At (Box 13)
  - Personality Files, Bl-Ea (Box 14)
  - Personality Files, En-Ha (Box 15)
  - Personality Files, Ha-La (Box 16)
  - Personality Files, La-Mu (Box 17)
  - Personality Files (Box 18)
  - Personality Files (Box 19)
  - Personality Files (Box 20)
  - Personality Files (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, Speeches, Writing, 1970s-1990s (Box 22)
  - Writing (Box 23)
  - Common Cause, 1970s-1980s (Box 24)
  - Correspondence (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1984 (Box 27)
  - White House Fellowships (Box 28)
  - White House Fellowships; Books (Box 29)
  - Desk Calendars (Box 30)
  - Writing, 1970-1972 (Box 36)
  - Writing, 1968-1969 (Box 37)
  - Writing, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
  - Writing, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - Writing, 1965, 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - Writing, 1978-1980 (Box 41)
  - Writing, 1975-1977 (Box 42)
  - Writing, 1981-1983 (Box 43)
  - Writing, 1984-1986 (Box 45)
  - JWG Memoirs - Tapes 1 + 1A JG Memoirs, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - D E Transitions Depression Tape 121, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape 2 - RTW, side A, side B = Hawaii beginning JG Memoirs, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape A Tare 6 - LBJ JG Memoirs May Have Left out 8A, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape C Carter continued Reagan, Bush, Clinton, not taken, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tapes - Nixon, Bobby Kennedy, JG Memoirs, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape D World War IIJG Memoirs, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape I - Hew Legislation bad tape, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - HEW (3) #15 bad tape, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape F Depression, Move East Hew (1) tape 13, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - Tape G - Hew Congress 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - HEW Congress 13, 14, Media 14, Tape H, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 48)
  - WW2 Revisited, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - WW2 Revisited 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - 5141135, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - A1518031, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - M80128, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - M80202, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - F1l207, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - M80129, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - CC-STAN, 2000-01; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - MFB, 2000 Feb 06; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - CGEL, 2000 Feb 06; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - CC-STAN, 2000 Jan; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - MFB, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - CGEL, 2000 Feb 06; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - MFB, 2000 Feb 06; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - Additions, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - Placerville, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - Additions BH, Stanford Hawaii Additions Billy Adams Whole Village to raise a childe, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - Hawaii / Round the World, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)
  - IB-GMAS/Youth, 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 48)